We want to encourage parent
participation, in lots of areas.
We want to start with the basics
and ensure good everyday contact,
so we really get to know the parents.
It starts with that.
Then we also want to take various steps
to involve parents in the centre.
We think that's important as parents
are their children's first educators.
So they should know about everything
their children do at out of school care
and we in turn want to know
what the children do at home.
Our team came up with
a number of activities
in which we thought it would be nice
to involve the parents.
One was a story-reading workshop,
where the mums and dads were invited
to the childcare centre.
They all brought books from home
to read out loud to our children.
The educators were there too
and it was a great atmosphere
with parents, children and educators.
Another example is mums who came
and took part in a dance workshop.
They danced with the children
and the educators.
We noticed that both the children
and the mums really, really enjoyed
doing an activity together with
each other and with the educators.
We have a good relationship
with the educators.
If you've been coming here
a few years,
there are some educators
who've been here a while too.
So they know an awful lot about us.
They know the problems at home too,
of course.
But they look after the children
really well.
Dorian was... I'm divorced now
and his godfather died recently too.
They looked after him really well
when it happened.
It's also nice for us
to be able to have a chat with them
in the evening sometimes.
They are a great support,
both for us and for the children.
They are always ready to help, always.
We use the parents' notice board
to announce the activities
we'll do this week,
but we also hang up photos of
the activities we've done.
Then the parents can see
what the children do here with us
but also which partners
the children go to,
so the parents can see
the work we do with partners.
Our parent contribution policy
is a very social one.
Parents pay according to their income.
People with the highest incomes
pay a reasonable amount
per half an hour.
And parents with the lowest income
pay 10 cents per half an hour.