In fact, we come here and play
but we play with the children
in an educational way.
It is a really great job.
There are new children every year.
And a wide range of activities.
It's not a typical nine-to-five job.
It is a great job
with an awful lot of variety.
Working with children is always exciting.
For me, being an educator
means playing and enjoying myself.
It also means preparing things,
finishing programmes, meeting deadlines.
I think children like coming to us
because, after sitting in class all day,
when they get here they can finally
spend their time in a fun,
lively and enjoyable way and relax.
Being an educator means
discovering new things every day,
including about yourself.
I really enjoy playing
with the children.
And helping them too, if they need it.
Because some children do need help.
Sometimes they just want
someone to talk to.
Just let yourself go and
have fun with the children.
Use your imagination,
enter the children's world.
We join in too and
I think that is important
because the children prefer that
and think it's more fun.
Some children don't like joining in.
But when they see us join in
they do too.
What I love doing is when the children
arrive in the morning, tired...
You try to wake them up.
In the morning we open the day
and dance and sing with the kids.
Then you see that the kids
are suddenly active and happy.
And that makes your day,
right from the start of it.
That's brilliant.